奥马哈
品质保证
两百年历史
辛那邦[美国烘焙连锁店]
内布拉斯加州
辛那邦
这一口  从未如此美味
这细节真不错
Yeah, that is some detail.
真是具有西部风情的细节
That is some western detail right there --
看看这西部风情的细节
Western detail, attention to detail.
看啊  他靴子背后竟然还有马刺
Look, he's even got the spurs on the back of his boots.
-还很锋利  -我喜欢
- And they are sharp. - I love it.
真的很锋利
They are.
介绍这件已经超时了  克里斯汀...
Well, the clock is gone on this piece, Christine, so...
天啊  那我们继续下一件
Oh, my goodness! Well, let's just move on.
人嘛  有时候是会犯错误  没事的
Well, from time to time, people make mistakes -- that's okay.
这是今晚第一件雷诺阿[法国画家]作品
This is our first Renoir of the evening.
是一件凹版作品  就是一种蚀刻画
This is a heliogravure, which is an etching.
1919年于巴黎  用一块铜板手工打造
It was hand-pulled from a copper plate in Paris in 1919.
我们之所以知道  是因为这背后的
We know this because that's what it says on the back,
防伪证书上面有写
where the certificate of authenticity is located.
真是高雅到了极致
Just as lovely as can be.
看看这柔和细腻的色差  极富阴柔之美
Look at the soft, delicate shading -- very feminine.
这可是限量版
This is a limited edition.
如果你钟爱雷诺阿的作品  千万不要错过
This is what you're looking for if you are a Renoir fan.
天啊  时间刚好
100 -- oh, my goodness. Right at the buzzer.
不错
Good.
非洲饼干陆龟是个例外
...of the few exceptions is the African pancake tortoise,
它有扁平且灵活的壳
which has a flat, flexible shell
可以让它藏匿于岩石裂缝中
that allows it to hide in rock crevasses.
一场大规模小到中雪
Big swath of light to moderate snow
从布罗肯鲍地区南下科尔尼  海斯廷斯
from the Broken Bow area down toward Kearney, Hastings,
格兰德岛  正朝我们这里前进
Grand Island -- that is all moving in our direction.
所以我认为  七点到八点左右
So I do think, around 7:00 to 8:00,
整个地区会开始持续降雪
the snow will become pretty steady here across the region
随着降雪向我们逼近
with all this moving on top of us,
能见度也会下降不少
and that's really gonna knock down visibilities.
当然
And, again,
今晚的道路很有可能会积雪
snow-covered roads are gonna be definitely likely this evening,
会变得更滑  比...
making it even slippier -- or more...
比现在外面的道路更滑
...more slippery than it is out there at this time.
有关部门已发布冬季天气预警
There's that winter-weather advisory in effect
直至明早
until very early tomorrow morning.
我们再来看降雪总量
We're gonna talk snowfall totals.
寒冷天气
Will bitter, cold weather
是否有助于解决今秋田地里
help break up the compaction issues
出现的土壤压实问题呢
we created this fall in our fields?
在今天的《钢铁对话》[一档农业节目]中
Well, we'll show you where it will and
我们将告诉你这一情况
where it won't during today's Iron Talk.
说起土壤压实
When it comes to compaction...
有两种不同类型的土壤压实
...there's really two different types of compaction.
一是垂直压实
There's vertical compaction,
二是水平压实
and there's horizontal compaction.
两者有很大差异
And there's a big difference.
如果是水平压实
With horizontal compaction,
冻融是没有什么用处的
there really isn't much hope for help from a freeze thaw.
因为坚硬紧实的地层膨胀
And the reason why, as that hard, compacted layer swells
在春天解冻后会重回原位
and then, in the spring, thaws back out and settles back down,
其实根本没有打破压实层
there's really no breaking up of the compaction.
而垂直空间上  压实层向外膨胀
With a vertical zone, when compaction swells out,
到春天就会破裂
and then it breaks up in the spring,
这样一来问题就好办了
then you can actually get a little bit of help.
如果在过度潮湿的情况下耕作
So if you have some horizontal compaction created by
导致出现了水平压实...
doing some tillage when it was a little too wet, or...
不要让虚假指控害你陷入不公平的公司
Don't let false allegations bully you into an unfair fight.
你好  我是索尔·古德曼  我会为你而战
Hi, I'm Saul Goodman, and I will do the fighting for you.
我能搞定任何指控
No charge is too big for me.
面临法律效力走投无路时  不如打给索尔
When legal forces have you cornered, better call Saul!
我会让你的案子撤销
I'll get your case dismissed.
我会给你应得的辩护  为什么
I'll give you the defense you deserve. Why?
因为我是律师索尔·古德曼
Because I'm Saul Goodman, attorney-at-law.
我既会调查  又会辩护  还会说服别人
I investigate, advocate, persuade,
最重要的是  我会打赢官司
and, most importantly, win! Win...win...win!
不如打给索尔
Better call Saul.
你是否感到绝望
Do you feel doomed?
是否遭受敌人威胁  自由难保
Have opponents of freedom wrongly intimidated you?
或许他们告诉你  你惹了大麻烦
Maybe they told you that you're in serious trouble
你束手无策  不知所措
and there's nothing you can do about it.
我是索尔·古德曼
I'm Saul Goodman,
让我来告诉你  他们错了
and I'm here to tell you that they're wrong.
争取正义  为时不晚  不如打给...
It's never too late for justice. Better call...
绝命律师
第一季第一集
新墨西哥州第二司法管辖区
公平
回想一下...  你的大脑...
Think back... your brain...
已经记不太清了
I-it's just not all there yet.
如果我们都要为19岁时做的事负责
If we were all held responsible for what we did when we were 19...
我还记得小时候的感觉  回想一下
I remember what it was like to be a kid. Think back.
告诉他们  法官大人  你怎么想
Tell 'em, judge, what would you say?
这些男孩儿  19岁
These boys -- 19.
我不能...  我不...
I can't -- I don't --
这三个年轻小伙儿
these three young men...
就像曾经的你们
Just like you.
女士们先生们  想象一下重返19岁的感觉
Oh, to be 19 again, you with me, ladies and gentlemen?
还记得你们的19岁吗
Do you remember 19?
十九岁时风华正茂
Let me tell you, the juices are flowing.
血气方刚  精力旺盛
The red corpuscles are corpuscling,
草地又绿又软
the grass is green, and it's soft,
夏日永不结束
and summer's gonna last forever.
你们还记得吗
Now, do you remember?
当然记得
Yeah, you do.
但说真的  扪心自问
But if you're being honest, I mean, well, really honest,
你们会想起来  那时的自己
you'll recall that you also had
还有一颗发育不全的19岁大脑
an underdeveloped 19-year-old brain.
就我个人来说  如果我要为
Me, personally, I-it, if I were held accountable
19岁时做出的蠢事负责
for some of the stupid decisions I made
我的天
when I was 19, oh, boy, wow.
我们现在要是在教堂
And I bet if we were in church right now,
你们都会向我说"阿门"[表示赞同]
I'd get a big "Amen!"
所以说回到本案主角
Which brings us to these three--
也就是这三个蠢货
now, these three knuckleheads,
很抱歉  但你们的确是蠢货
and I'm sorry, boys, but that's what you are--
他们做了件蠢事  这点无可否认
they did a dumb thing. We're not denying that.
不过  我想请各位记住两点重要事实
However, I would like you to remember two salient facts.
第一  没有人受伤  完全没有
Fact one, nobody got hurt, not a soul.
这点非常重要
Very important to keep that in mind.
第二  控方一直
Fact two, now, the prosecution
揪着"非法闯入"这个词不放
keeps bandying this term "Criminal trespass."
斯宾诺佐先生  也就是房子的主人
Mr. Spinowzo, the property owner,
向我们承认  他大部分的店铺
admitted to us that he keeps most portions of his business
日夜向公众开放
open to the public both day and night.
闯入
So, trespassing?
这个词有点过了  不是吗  戴夫
That's a bit of a reach, don't you think, Dave?
据我所知
Here's what I know--
这三位年轻人  几乎都是荣誉学生
these three young men, near honors students all,
周六晚有点兴奋
were feeling their oats one Saturday night,
脑袋不清楚  干了些傻事
and they just... went a little bananas.
我也说不清
I don't know.
你们可以当我疯了  但我认为
Call me crazy, but I don't think they deserve
他们的大好前程
to have their bright futures ruined
不应被一时迷失心智
by a momentary, minute,
永不会再犯的小错毁掉
never-to-be-repeated lapse of judgment.
各位  所谓大人不记小人过
Ladies and gentlemen, you're bigger than that.
-肯尼  你在录吗  -在录  等一下
- Kenny, Kenny, are you rolling? - Yeah, yeah. Wait a minute.
老兄  小声点  别这么激动
But, dude, but, dude, pipe down. Chill out, would you?
沃特森老师第四节生物课的同学们
Hey, Mrs. Watson's fourth-period biology class,
这个是专门为你准备的  好好学着吧
this one's for you. Watch and learn, losers.
-天呐  -怎么都没有血
- Oh, God! - Dude! Where did all the blood go?!
他都死了  血早就抽干了
Dude, he's dead. they suck it all out, dumbass.
真棒  他们把血放到哪去了
Awesome. Where do they put it?
我现在切到颈骨了
All right, I'm though the neck bone now, dude.
-真棒  -肯尼  到这来
- Oh, nice. - Kenny, get over here, man.
我弄好了  把它拿走
I'm-I'm getting it. Get this out of here.
好吧
All right. All right, fine.
让我来
Here, let me do it.
-我能行  -好吧
- I got it! - All right.
-拿着  -天呐
- Get that. All right. - Oh, my God.
让我来
Here, let me do it.
走开
Dude, get off!
别激动
Chill out.
好吧  等等
All right. Wait, wait.
等等
Okay, wait for it. Wait.
-终于弄下来了  -这位老兄真是
- Come on! Yeah, baby, yeah! - This dude was-
我猜你肯定会把小弟弟放进他喉咙里
Dude, I dare you to stick your wang in the throat hole.
你放我就放
I will if you will, loser.
好吧
All right, all right!
七百美金
收款人 詹姆斯·麦吉尔
你不会算数吗
What the hell kind of math is that?
一场辩护700美金
$700 per defense.
不是辩护  是"委托人" "人"
No, no, no. "Defendant." "...dant."
三个人一共2100  真是便宜
Three defendants, $2,100, which, by the way, bargain--
我可是据理力争
what I did for them.
可人家还是要去蹲监狱啊
They going to jail, ain't they?
这跟钱有什么关系
So, since when does that matter?!
他们操了一颗死人头
They had sex with a head!
没人让你一次代理三个人
Look, didn't nobody tell you to try all three of them together.
一次庭审只有700美金
One trial, $700.
你会想我的  你肯定会想我
You're gonna miss me. You are gonna miss me.
我告诉你  就算天下红雨
Cause it'll be a cold day in hell
我也不会再为这个傻逼法庭做公设律师
before I do any more P.D. work for this shitty court!
再见  宝贝
Sayonara, baby!
祝你过得愉快
You have yourself a nice day.
詹姆斯·麦吉尔法律办公室
Law offices of James McGill.
请问找哪位
How may I direct your call?
凯特尔曼夫人  很高兴您能再次来电
Yes, Mrs. Kettleman, so good of you to return.
麦吉尔先生此时不在办公室
A-actually, I don't have Mr. McGill at the moment,
但是他...
but I know he'd--
棒极了
Oh, splendid.
很抱歉  我们的办公室正在刷漆
Unfortunately, our offices are being painted
到处都乌烟瘴气的
and the fumes are quite horrid.
他能否与您和您的丈夫
Could he meet you and your husband at, say,
在中心路的洛约拉咖啡店见面
Uh, Loyola's cafe on central?
那就约四点  再见
4:00 it shall be. Cheers.
三块
$3.
我认证过了  看到贴纸了吗
Uh, I'm validated. See the stickers?
是  有五张贴纸
Well, I see five stickers.
少了一张  三块
You're one shy. It's $3.
他们给了我...  听着
They gave me -- look.
我今天全天都可以免费进出  好吗
I'm validated for the entire day, okay?
五张贴纸  六张贴纸  我才不管什么鬼贴纸
Five stickers, six stickers -- I don't know from stickers.
因为我在那里出庭
Because I was in that court back there
为了救人命  所以...
saving people's lives, so...
别装逼
Well, gee, that's swell.
谢谢你让我重建了对司法系统的信任
And thank you for restoring my faith in the judicial system.
但你现在要么付三块钱  要么回去
Now you either pay the $3, or you go back inside
再弄一张贴纸
and you get an additional sticker.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
行  你赢了  祝贺你
Fine. You win. Hooray for you.
倒车
Backing up!
我得倒车  我得再去弄贴纸
I have to back up! I need more stickers!
我的贴纸不够
Don't have enough stickers!
谢谢  谢谢你  你人真好
Thank you! Thank you -- very nice!
他是本月最佳员工
Employee of the month over here!
没错
Yeah!
祝贺他  给他颁奖牌吧
Hooray! Give him a medal!
没事  别紧张  行吗
Don't do anything, guys. Just relax, all right?
我只是疑惑  为什么你觉得他得雇律师
Well, I'm just fuzzy as to why you think he needs a lawyer.
我觉得克雷格处理公事完美无瑕
I mean, Craig, the way you run your office is beyond reproach.
没错  完美无瑕
Yeah. Beyond reproach.
-没错  -我办事小心
- Yeah. - I'm a stickler, you know, for --
确实  钱方面他很小心
He is. He's a stickler with the money.
-他办事的确小心  -没错
- He's definitely a stickler. - Yeah. Yeah.
我肯定他没犯罪
I mean, he's certainly not guilty of some...
肯定没有  他遵纪守法
Is certainly not. He's innocent of any wrongdoing.
我非常清楚
That's abundantly clear to me.
其实我也不会为罪犯当代理律师
And frankly, I don't go looking for guilty people to represent.
没必要去趟浑水  是吧
I mean who needs that aggravation, right?
没错
Right.
我的信息都是从报纸上看来的
Look, all I know is what I read in the paper.
县财政局的钱
And typically, when money goes missing
不翼而飞  金额达到了
from the county treasury -- and the number here is,
160万美元...
Uh, $1.6 million...
-那是会计...  -会计核算差额
- Well, that's an accounting... - It's an accounting discrepancy.
确实是核算差额
It's a discrepancy, absolutely.
不过一般呢  出现核算差额
But typically, when that happens,
警方就会找财务主管
the police look at the treasurer.
既然主管就是...
And since that person is, uh --
我只是觉得你该抓住主动权
I just think a little proactivity may be in order.
-好吧  -我只是...
- Well... - You know, I just
觉得雇律师会显得很可疑
think I'd look guilty if I hired a lawyer.
-没错  -不
- Yeah. - No.
其实被捕才让别人觉得你有罪
Actually, it's getting arrested that makes people look guilty,
即便你是无辜的
Even the innocent ones,
但每天都有无辜的人被捕
and innocent people get arrested every day.
他们最后被关在小房间里
And they find themselves in a little room
警探假装是他们最好的朋友
with a detective who acts like he's their best friend.
"告诉我"  警探说  "帮我查清此案"
"Talk to me," He says. Uh, "Help me clear this thing up.
"你不用请律师  只有罪犯才需要律师"
You don't need a lawyer -- only guilty people need lawyers."
你就中招了
And boom!
一失足成千古恨
Hey, that's when it all goes south.
这时候你就需要一个人帮你
That's when you want someone in your corner,
不遗余力地帮你
someone who will fight tooth and nail.
律师就像健康保险
Lawyers -- you know, we're like health insurance.
谁都希望自己用不着
You hope you never need it.
但没有可不行
But, man, oh, man, not having it -- no.
接下来怎么办
How would we proceed
-如果我们决定  -行  这是一份
- if we decided to, uh... - Oh, well, this is a...
约定函
...letter of engagement.
非常简洁明了
It's very simple, straightforward.
请仔细阅读  但如果签约
Please, uh, read it closely, but if you sign it, um,
我将马上开始制定辩护策略
I can get started - on that defense strategy of ours
下午就能开始
this very afternoon.
克雷格...
Craig...
我觉得可以明天再说
I think maybe we should sleep on it.
好吧...  当然
Uh...sure.
你觉得呢  麦吉尔先生
Don't you think, Mr. McGill?
也许我们可以明天再说
Maybe we should sleep on it.
叫我"吉米"就好
Oh, oh, please, call me "Jimmy."
当然可以
A-absolutely.
反正不急
I mean, there's no rush.
对了...  克雷格  我们得去接孩子了
You -- - oh, and, you know, Craig, we got to pick up the kids...
-没错  -就在...  是啊
- Oh. Right. - Yeah. ...at the...yeah. Right.
我们再联系
Well, uh, we will be in touch.
谢谢你请我们喝咖啡  提建议
Oh. Uh, thank you for the coffee and for the advice.
真是太客气了
You're very, very welcome.
给  拿着
Um, here. Take this.
这上面有我的电话号码
It's, uh -- it's got my phone number on it.
-好  行  -知道了
- Yeah. Okay. - Got it.
号码是94560054
The number is 9456-0054
4896-0643,
到期日是十一月四日
And the expiration is 11/04.
关键词是"优等"
Okay, and the keyword here is "Classy," all right?
超优等  只用那些看上去很昂贵
Super classy -- use only flowers that look expensive,
但其实很廉价的花
but, you know, aren't.
纸条上应该写  "亲爱的贝茜和克雷格
Uh, and the note should say "Dear Betsy and Craig,"
你们的正义使者在此献上祝福
Uh, "Best wishes from your stickler for justice,
詹姆斯·麦吉尔"
James McGill."
知道了吗  麦吉尔的拼写是...
Okay? And "McGill" is spelled "M-c--"
再查一遍  不不不  已经付了钱的
Well, run it again. Oh, no, no, no. It's paid up.
再查一遍
Run it again.
天呐  天呐  天呐
Oh, God! Oh, God! Oh, God!
天呐
Oh, my God! Ohh.
卡尔  卡尔  看着我
Cal, Cal! Look at me!
伙计  看着我  你没事吧
Buddy, look at me. Are you okay?
说句话吧  你都干了些什么
Say something. What did you do?
-我...  -你对我弟弟干了什么
- I did -- - What did you do to my brother?
你开车的时候怎么不看路
Why don't you look where you're going?!
我正在转弯  他突然冒了出来
I was making a turn! He came out of nowhere!
你他妈把他撞飞了
You freaking -- freaking hit him, man!
-我...  -你从他身上碾了过去
- I did-- - You ran him over!
你从我弟弟身上碾了过去
You ran over my brother!
我把整个过程都拍下来了
And I got the whole thing on video.
这是场意外  是意外
It was an accident. It was an accident.
他不是  他不是故意的  我先...
He didn't -- he didn't mean to. Let me just -- aah! Aah! Oh!
-不  -这边断了
- No, no. - That's broke. That's broke.
-我的腿  -你把他腿撞断了
- It's my leg. Oh! - You broke his leg.
你开车都不注意周围吗
Why are you driving around and not looking?!
开车就是为了撞断别人的腿吗
Driving around, breaking people's legs!
这...行了  冷静点
It's -- it's o-- it's -- okay, okay, okay!
手机在哪里...  来人啊  快报警
Where's the -- Somebody call the cops!
别  别叫警察
Don't call -- don't call the police.
-不要报警  -报警
- Don't call the police. - Police!
-拉斯  -警察呢[西语]
- Lars. - La policia!
-别别别  别叫他们  -我自己打电话
- Don't, don't, don't. Don't call them. - I'll call them myself.
-我要自己报警  -不要报警
- I'm doing it myself. - Don't call the police.
不要报警
Don't call the police.
-不要叫警察吗  -不要
- Don't call the cops? - No.
那你打算怎么办
How you gonna fix this?
你准备怎么补偿我们
What are you gonna do to make things right?
我不知道  伙计
I don't know, fellas.
我该怎么补偿你们
What can I do to make it right?
我不知道
I don't know.
五百块
$500.
500 bucks?
是吗
Yeah?
搞什么啊  兄弟
Ow! What the hell, man?!
听着  星光快车兄弟
Listen, Starlight Express,
音乐剧  演员穿旱冰鞋
我给你俩的演技打9.6分
I'm gonna give you a 9.6 for technique,
挑选目标的眼光打0分
0.0 for choice of victim.
我是个律师
I'm a lawyer.
再说了  你们真的觉得开这种老爷车的人
Furthermore, does -- does this steaming pile of crap
身上有油水可以搾吗
scream "payday" to you, huh?!
里面要是坐个一晚三百的小姐
The only way that entire car is worth 500 bucks
这辆车才能卖到五百元
is if there's a $300 hooker sitting in it.
我们来谈谈撞坏挡风玻璃得赔多少线
Now, let's talk about what you owe me for the windshield.
你们  干什么
You -- what?
用支票也行
I'll take a check!
你好  女士们  你们好
Chao chi c'ung, ladies! Chao chi c'ung!
您好
Chao chi c'ung!
你好  阮太太
Chao chi c'ung, Mrs. Nguyen.
你真是迷人...
My, don't you look --
有我的信吗
Got my mail?
把死人头切下来操  你还帮他们打官司
You work for people who have sex with chopped-off head?
-都登报纸了吗  -我表兄告诉我的
- Was it in the paper? - I heard it from my cousin.
为什么啊  你为什么给这种人干活
Why? Why you work for these people?
我运气好吧
Just lucky, I guess.
只有顾客才能享用黄瓜水
Cucumber water for customer only!
詹姆斯·麦吉尔律所
您没有语音留言
You have...zero messages.
麦吉尔先生
根据您和霍华德·哈姆林先生的谈话  特为您寄来支票
哈姆林麦吉尔联合律所
布兰达  今儿这发型不错
Brenda, looking good. Nice do.
维达大人[黑武士]去哪了
Uh, where's Lord Vader?
他没准备好见您
Uh, he's not quite ready for you yet.
南会议室吗
South conference room.
不如您在这等会
How about you wait out here?
我还是别等了
How about I don't?
-法兰西斯先生  -詹姆斯
- Oh, Sir Francis. - James.
您和往常一样精神
Well-groomed, as always.
-好吧  -好的
- Okay. - All right.
基斯  卡伦
Keith, Karen, yes.
你干预了自然的原始力量  哈姆林先生
You have meddled with the primal forces of nature, Mr. Hamlin,
语出1976年电影《电视台风云》
我不会坐视不理
And I won't have it!
需要我叫保安吗
Do you want me to call security?
没关系  布兰达  交给我们吧
It's okay, Brenda, we got it.
你们好  杰克  内特  艾伦
Hey, Jack. Hey, Nate. Hey, Aaron.
有何贵干  吉米
What can we do for you, Jimmy?
对不起  都怪这张桌子
I'm sorry. It's -- it's this table.
我有点情不自禁
Something just comes over me.
你可以告诉我这两万六
You can tell me what this, uh, $26,000
是用来干什么的
is supposed to be for.
那是给查克的钱  这不是你想要的结果吗
That's money for Chuck. Isn't that what you wanted?
区区两万六
A measly 26 grand?
这就像彼得·米努伊特对印第安人所做的事
Jesus, you're like Peter Minuit with the Indians.
1626年彼得·米努伊特
用价值24美元的珠子和饰物从当地印第安人手里买下了曼哈顿
心情好就扔一些珠子和贝壳给他们
Throw in some beads and shells while you're at it.
这只是个开始
It's just a start.
还会有更多的...
There'll be more --
除非你打算撕碎所有支票
unless you're gonna just tear them all up.
为什么是我收到  为什么不是查克
And why was it made out to me -- why not Chuck?
他能自己去银行吗
Can he make his way to the bank?
我只是认为让你转交
I just assumed it was best
这样最好
to have the money go through you.
我们可以按照你的意愿来完成
We can do it any way you want.
这事不算完  霍华德
This isn't going away, Howard.
查克为这间事务所做的一切
What Chuck did for this firm --
他几乎是一个人完成的
and damn near single-handedly --
这里的三分之一都应该属于他
1/3 of this place belongs to him.
是的  比如这里有十二把椅子
Yeah. What do you got -- 12 chairs here?
那其中就有四把是查克的
Four of these chairs are Chuck's.
你有五个这种发光装置吗
You got five of these light thingumajigs?
那一又三分之二个是查克的
Uh, mm, 1 2/3 are Chuck's.
你们面前有六个丹麦面包  六个吗
Yeah. Six -- how many Danishes -- six Danishes?
-所有面包都可以给你  -不不
- You can have all the Danish you want, Jimmy. - No, no.
他们都属于查克  而查克不是贪心的人
They're Chuck's Danishes, and Chuck isn't greedy,
所以他只要两个...
so h-he'll just take two...
再加上大约一千七百万美元
plus $17 million -- in that ballpark.
我们会知道的
I mean, we'll know
只要我们让会计人员到这里转一圈
once we get the accountants poking around here.
在那之前  不用开什么小额支票
Until then, no more penny-ante checks
好像查克还在这里工作似的
designed to make it look like Chuck still works here.
他不在这里了  再也不会回来了
He doesn't. He never will again.
是时候还他公平  并付钱给他了
It's time to do right by him and cash him out.
你转达的这些都是查克自己的意愿吗
So, these are Chuck's own wishes that you're conveying?
这是他最好的选择
This is what's best for him.
是他亲口告诉你
So he personally told you that it's his wish
他想退出事务所吗
to withdraw from the firm?
看来不是  不然我真得吓一跳
See, that would surprise me.
距离他来这里已经快一年了
It's been nearly a year since he's set foot in here.
-我只是为他争取最大利益  -我也是
- I'm just doing what's in his best interests. - So am I.
而我相信他将会很乐意看到这些
And I, for one, believe he's gonna lick this thing.
在他回归之前  他的办公室会保持原样
Until then, his office is just as he left it.
他的秘书也依然有薪水
His secretary's still on payroll.
如果查克把这叫作延长休假
If Chuck can call this an extended sabbatical,
那我们也可以  他对我们就是这么重要
then so can we -- he's that important to us.
这样吧  还是让陪审团来裁定
You know what? Let's let a jury figure it out.
是啊  他们会很爱你的  霍华德
Yeah, they're gonna love you, Howard.
你是那么务实并且可靠
You're so down-to-earth and relatable.
而你...  必将...  赎罪
And you...will...atone!
是《电视台风云》里尼德·巴蒂说的话
It's Ned Beatty, from "Network."
天呐  你们怎么什么都不知道
For christ's sakes, guys.
吉米
Jimmy.
我差点忘了  这个月的法院立案
I almost forgot -- this month's filings.
可以帮我省下邮寄费了
You could save me the postage.
刚才你听到我说的话了吗
W-weren't you listening in there?
查克已经不在这里工作了
Chuck doesn't work here anymore.
你认为我会帮你建立书面记录吗
You think I'm gonna help you establish a paper trail?
-吉米  -不  别想把屎盆子往他身上扣
- Now, Jimmy -- - No, stop trying to pawn that shit off on him.
吉米
Jimmy.
吉米  有时候在我们这行里
You know, Jimmy, sometimes, in our line of work,
容易被取胜的欲望冲昏头脑
you can get so... caught up in the idea of winning
却忘记倾听自己内心的声音
that you forget to listen to your heart.
替我向查克问好  好吗
Give Chuck my love, would you?
原来你在这里啊
Oh, there you are.
贝茜  克雷格
Betsy, Craig.
你好  好的
Hi. Okay.
你今天真漂亮
You look lovely today.
谢谢你这么说
Oh, thank you so much.
你能不能...
Couldn't you just --
你明知我做不到
You know, I can't.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
你手机什么的放信箱了吗
Ground yourself?
是的  放了
Yes, I grounded myself.
你不能再买培根肉了
You got to stop putting bacon on the list,
因为冰箱看起来就像一锅炖旋毛虫
'cause that cooler's looking like a trichinosis stew.
来得正好
Perfect timing.
"布兰斯·弗格森教授"
"Professor Brans Vogelson."
"赫尔辛基大学"
"University of Helsinki"?
是的  你必须把这些翻译过来
Yeah, you're gonna have to get that translated.
-翻译成瑞典语吗  -芬兰语
- Into Swedish? - Finnish.
芬兰语  翻译成...
Finnish, uh, translating into...
我相信新墨西哥大学会有人可以做到
I'm sure there's someone at UNM who can do that.
你知道我打算开一间律师事务所  不是吗
You do know I'm trying to start a legal practice, right?
弗格森正在研究电磁场
Vogelson's been working on the effects
对斑马鱼的影响  还有...
of electromagnetic fields on zebra fish -- and, oh!
《金融时报》
Financial Times.
是啊  我知道你想看
Yeah, I knew you missed it,
所以我想  "管他呢"
so I figured, "What the heck?"
谢谢你  我知道这很贵
Thank you. I know it's expensive.
拿着
Here.
不用  没关系的
That's not -- it's all right.
-我可不希望你自掏腰包  -我...
- I don't expect you to go out of pocket. - I...
拿去  你的酬劳
Go ahead -- reimburse yourself.
谢谢
Thanks.
查克  你能不能先别看那个
Hey, Chuck, um, can you not read that for a second?
我们能谈谈吗
Can we talk?
你还好吗
Are you all right?
你看起来很憔悴
You look peaked.
我没事  请坐下
I'm fine. Please, just sit.
你没遇到麻烦
You're not in trouble.
你得从律所撤股了
Um... You got to cash out.
必须得
You got to.
-又来了  不是吧  -没有别的选择了
- Again? Really? - There's no other way.
我知道你不想听这些  可你必须这样做
I know that you don't want to hear it, but you've got to.
你知道我能渡过这一劫
You know I'm going to beat this.
你知道我会好起来的
You know I'm going to get better.
-当然  -那么
- Yeah, sure. - Well, then,
就没什么好说的了
there's nothing more to talk about.
我会渡过这一劫
I will beat this.
由此  从错误的原理推导[拉丁法律用语]
Ergo, a falsis principiis proficisci.
-意思是  -那不是...
- Meaning? - That's not --
-意思是  -那是说原理错误  可我
- Meaning? - That's the one about false principles, but it's not --
你从错误的原理得出结论
You proceed from false principles.
你的辩论毫无根基
Your argument is built on quicksand.
因此也就不攻自破了
Therefore, it collapses.
对对  你没在听我说话
Yeah, yeah. You're not listening.
好吧
Fine.
让我们得出合乎逻辑的结论
Let's take this to its logical conclusion.
为了支付我的股份
In order to pay out my share,
假设我的合伙人会被迫清算律所
suppose my partners are forced to liquidate the firm.
-然后呢  -那是他们的问题
- Then what? - That's their problem.
我的委托人会被扫地出门
My clients are out in the cold.
我的案子都要完蛋
My cases are scattered to the winds.
一百二十六个人会失业
126 people lose their jobs.
你那些收发室的好朋友该怎么办
What happens to your cronies in the mailroom,
还有那些律师  律师助理  保洁工人
the assistants, the paralegals, the janitorial staff?
全都会流落街头
All of them, out on the street.
你的好朋友金  一份好前途转眼成灰
Your friend Kim -- a promising career -- over and done with.
一切都是哈姆林欠你的
Hamlin owes you everything.
你一手打造了这间律所
You built that place single-handedly
他那时还在四山俱乐部练习沙坑球呢
while he was out at Four Hills working on his bunker shot.
不要说那么夸张  我是帮了忙而已
Let's not exaggerate. I helped.
帮忙而已
You helped.
所以就更没必要为了点小钱
All the more reason not to tear it down
把这一切都毁了啊
just for a little bit of cash.
听我说  查克  我快完了  好吗
Look...Chuck, I'm going under -- okay? --
第三次接手这些狗屁合约官司...
For the third time with these bull-crap contract counsel --
怎么是"狗屁"
"Bull crap"?
这些七百块一件的狗屁小公设律师活
Bull-crap, pissant P.D. cases at 700 bucks a shot.
公设辩护律师可是律师最难得的经历之一
Public-defender work is some of the best experience there is.
我刚刚经手一个案子  查克  三个委托人
I just had a case, Chuck, with three clients --
提讯  预审  庭审
Uh, arraignments, voir dire, jury trial --
全套下来
The whole nine yards.
你知道我挣了多少钱吗  七百块
You know what I took home? 700 bucks.
还不如去贫民窟卖血赚得多
Yeah, I might as well head down to skid row and sell plasma.
你代表的都是些走投无路的人
You're representing people who have nowhere else to turn.
钱不是问题
The money is beside the point.
钱就是问题
Money is not beside the point -- money is the point.
我一直告诉你  要有耐心
I keep telling you -- have patience.
没有捷径可走
There are no shortcuts.
把工作干好  自然会有委托人找上门
Do good work, and the clients will come.
自然会有委托人找上门  对  我明白
The clients will come. Yeah, I know.
好吧
Okay.
对天发誓
Hand to God,
我本不打算这样说  可你破产了
I wasn't gonna say this, but you are broke.
我负担不了我们两个人
I can't carry both of us.
我已经使出了吃奶的劲  可我做不到
I've been trying like hell, but I can't.
你这是在说什么
Well, you're saying what?
你以为我需要你来养吗
You think you have to provide for me?
我从没让你这样做
I never asked you that.
你根本不用开口  好吗
You didn't have to ask, okay?
我已经尽我最大努力了
I've been doing my damnedest,
但我也快熬到头了
but the day of reckoning is here.
很快  查克  你就要流落街头了
Soon, Chuck, you're gonna be out on the street
到时候全世界的电磁场都会碾过你
with all the electromagnetism in the world raining down on you.
拜托  拜托  好好想象一下那场景
Now, please, please, picture that,
然后再告诉我钱不是问题
then tell me that money is beside the point.
让你烦恼的就是这事吗
This is what has you all worked up?
对
Yeah!
吉米  没什么好担心的
Jimmy...There's nothing to worry about.
-给  -这是什么
- Here. - What is this?
一笔津贴  以后每周都会有
A stipend -- there's gonna be one every week.
哈姆林麦吉尔联合律所给的857美元
$857 from Hamlin Hamlin & Mcgill?
我会一分不差地还给他们
I'm gonna pay them back -- every penny.
我本不想要的  但霍华德坚持要给我
I didn't want to take anything, but Howard was very insistent.
我也会全还给你的
And I'm gonna pay you back, too.
等等  哈姆林来过了吗
Wait, Hamlin was here?
我又不是闭门谢客的隐士
It's not like I'm a recluse.
怎么  他把手机留在信箱里了吗
What? He put his cellphone in the mailbox?
他理解我的情况
He understands the situation.
他真的放了吗
He grounded himself?
当然
Of course.
然后你们两个达成一致  既然众所周知
And the two of you agreed that since, as everybody knows,
你随时都可能回去工作
you're going back to work any day now,
律所理应帮你贴补家用
that the firm should help you make ends meet.
除去你话里的讽刺味  正是这样
That's correct, minus the sarcasm.
哈姆林这是把你当傻子玩
Hamlin's making you a chump!
我会好起来的
I'm going to get better!
我会回去工作
I'm gonna go back to work,
从哪里跌倒就从哪里爬起来
and I'm picking up where I left off!
对不起
Sorry.
查克  对不起
Sorry, Chuck.
我知道  你一直都想帮我
I understand that you're trying to look out for me,
但你现在因小失大了
but you're missing the bigger picture.
我知道
I got it.
还有件事
Speaking of which...
霍华德拿来了这个
Howard brought this.
他有点担忧
He's concerned.
什么
What?
你得承认  这容易让人混淆
You have to admit -- it could be confusing --
他的公司名是哈姆林·哈姆林·麦吉尔
Hamlin, Hamlin, Mcgill?
你的律所叫詹姆斯·M·麦吉尔
James M. Mcgill?
我就叫这名字
That's my name.
我打小就叫这名字
I was born with it. I...
那也不行
Still...
要不改叫先锋律所吧
How about Vanguard Law?
-那直布罗陀法律公司怎么样  -等等
- Or Gi...Gibraltar Legal... - Wait, wait.
所以因为哈姆林  我还不能用自己的名字了
So I'm not supposed to use my name o-on Hamlin's say-so?
他这是什么意思  要起诉我吗
W-- what's he gonna do -- sue me?
谁也不想给自己找麻烦
Nobody wants to create an adversarial situation.
霍华德肯定愿意付钱给你
I'm sure Howard would gladly pay the cost
做个新火柴盒广告
of new matchbooks and so on.
这只是职业礼节罢了
It's simply a matter of professional courtesy.
查克  你到底是哪边的
Chuck, whose side are you on?
什么哪边不哪边
There are no sides.
不过  吉米
But, Jimmy...
你难道不想打出自己的牌子吗
Wouldn't you rather build your own identity?
别总想沾别人的光
Why ride on someone else's coattails?
霍华德  你想跳舞吗
You want to dance, Howard?
那我们就跳吧
Let's dance.
滑
Go!
你能不能滑得再靠近我一点  废物
No, you can get closer than that, you bitch.
快点
Come on.
对  就这样
And here it comes.
不错  好点儿了
There you go. Better.
我滑得怎么样
How was that?
都给你录了  你看
It's right on here. Take a look.
还是那句话  身体要绷紧
Still, tighter is everything.
绷紧  什么呀  什么绷紧
T-tighter? What? T-tighter what?
我也说不清  就是站着的时候要绷紧
I don't know. Just stand...Tighter.
-你听懂没  -没有
- You know what I mean? - I don't know what you mean.
你真笨  就是选择一种风格
That sucked. We can call that a stylistic choice, I guess,
-如果你想  -你们俩
- If you want to... - Hey, fellas.
我这里有大生意给你们
We got business.
你怎么知道我们在这里
How did you find us?
挺奇怪的  是吧
I know, eerie, right?
等等  就耽误你们30秒
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Come on. Give me 30 seconds.
这说不定是你们人生中最有价值的30秒
Could be the most profitable 30 seconds of your lives.
我给你们讲个故事吧  有个小伙子
Let me tell you about a young guy.
他其实和你们差不多大
Actually, he's about your age.
住在离这里很远的地方
He lived a long way from here
就在伊利诺伊州的西塞罗市
in a town called Cicero, Illinois.
在那里  他可是个人物
And in Cicero, he was the man.
这么说吧  他走在街上
I mean, when he strolled down the street,
所有小混混都会和他击掌打招呼
all the corner boys would give him the high five.
所有漂亮妞儿都会冲他笑
All the finest babes would smile at him
巴望着他也能回一个笑容
and hope that he would smile back.
大家都叫他"风流吉米"
They called him "Slippin' Jimmy,"
所有人都想和他做朋友
and everybody wanted to be his friend.
"风流吉米"
"Slippin' Jimmy"?
这是什么狗屁绰号
What the hell kind of name is that?
听我说
Well, I'll tell you, now --
西塞罗的冬天冷得能冻死人
Winters in Cicero are murder.
你们在金色的西部长大的
You guys growing up out here in the golden west --
根本体会不到那有多冷
y-you don't know, okay?
那里的冬天能把你的鼻涕冻住
I'm talking cold that'll freeze the snot right in your nose.
那寒风能割裂你的夹克衫
I'm talking wind that'll cut through your jacket
金厨 著名厨房刀具品牌
然后像一把金厨刀一样把你切碎
And carve you up like a Ginsu knife.
总之  西塞罗的大部分居民都很害怕冬天
In fact, most folks in Cicero were scared of winter,
但吉米可不怕
but not Jimmy.
夏天的时候  他就等啊等
Jimmy waited around all summer,
九月终于来了
and when September finally rolled around
他感受到了第一股凉风
and he'd feel that first cold wind
从密歇根湖吹来  他知道  它要来了
come sweeping off Lake Michigan, he knew it was coming.
宽扎节  非裔美国人节日
他等的是圣诞节吗  是宽扎节吗
Was it Christmas? Was it Kwanzaa?
都不是  是一年一度的碰瓷季
Better -- it was Slip 'n Fall season.
很快  等到外面已经变得非常冷
Soon as it was cold enough,
他就找一块光滑结冰的地面
he'd find a nice, smooth patch of ice.
州级公路也行  密歇根大道更好
State street was good. Michigan Avenue was better.
他选好点  等到路上人多的时候
He'd pick his spot, wait for it to get busy,
他就踩着那冰片滑过去  然后  轰的一声
Then he'd walk out on the ice, and -- boom!
他摔得那么狠
He would biff it so hard,
五个街区外的人都跑来看
people would come running from five blocks away.
那他碰瓷碰成了吗
Yeah, but did he collect?
"成了吗"
"Did he collect?"
"风流吉米"从来没失败过
Slippin' jimmy had it dialed in, all right?
摔一次  他就能要来六千或者八千块
One good fall -- he'd clear 6, 8 grand.
那些钱够他每天喝老密尔沃基酒  吸大麻
That'd keep him in Old Milwaukee and maui wowie
一直用到劳动节
right through Labor Day.
八千块啊
8 grand?
没错
8 grand.
我觉得你们都是潜力股
Now, see, I look at you guys, I see potential.
你们用滑板碰瓷很妙
The skateboard's a nice wrinkle --
全年都可以干
that makes it a year-round gig.
很明显  你非常清楚怎么去摔  对吗
And clearly, you know how to take a header, right?
但我得问你  收成最好的一天
But I got to ask you -- your best day ever,
赚了多少钱
how much did you clear?
-630  -630
- $630. - $630.
六百三十块吗
630 bucks.
是摔一次的钱数吗
Was that for one fall?
-两次  -一天摔两次
- Two. - Two falls in one day.
即使是你们这年纪  也会很疼吧
Even at your age, that's got to hurt.
确实疼啊
True that.
好吧  我给你们一个活儿
All right, well, I got a job for you.
两千块怎么样
How's 2 grand sound?
摔一次给两千块吗
2 grand for one hit?
就一次
One hit.
而且  你还能跟最好的人学习
Plus, you get to learn from the best.
船不错
Nice boat.
是啊  藏得很隐蔽
Yeah, discreet,
就跟清真寺里的钢管舞杆一样
like a stripper pole in a mosque.
别管那船了  看那辆车
Yeah, forget the boat. Look at the car.
知道是什么车吗
You know what that is?
不知道  旅行车吗
I don't know. A station wagon?
那是辆水星  1988年的水星黑貂休旅车
It's a Mercury, a 1988 Mercury Sable wagon.
记住它  烙在脑子里  记住了吗
Remember it. Burn it into your brains. You got it?
没问题  水星黑貂休旅车
It's a Mercury Sable Wagon, sure.
闭上眼  车是什么颜色
Close your eyes. What color is it?
-棕色  -棕色
- Brown. - Brown.
不  是中檀色  闭着眼睛
No, it's medium sandalwood. Keep your eyes closed.
车牌号开始是几
How does the license plate start?
-4  -4
- 4. - 4.
给你们一个金星奖章
Give those gentlemen a gold star.
她的名字是贝茜·凯特尔曼
Betsy Kettleman's her name.
每个工作日2点25和2点50之间
Every weekday between 2:25 and 2:50,
她都会经过这里去基特·卡森小学
she comes through here on her way to pick up her kids
接孩子
at Kit Carson elementary.
现在你需要找到一个她会减速的地方
Now, you need a place where she's gonna slow down --
-我说的对吗  -是的
- Am I right? - Yeah.
好了  在那儿  她减速了
All right. Well, there you go. She slows down.
她稍往右靠  你从那边冲出来
She hangs a right. You come shooting out of there.
把你对我那一套拿出来  翻个屁滚尿流
You do what you did to me. You go ass over teakettle.
摔出一流水平
You make it a blue-ribbon special.
她从车上下来以后
When she gets out of the car,
你正疼得要命  对吗
you're sufferin' St. Sebastian, right?
你是重头戏  知道吗  直接走到她面前
You're the hammer, okay? You get in her face.
把她吓到灵魂出窍
You scare the bejesus out of her.
把手机给我
Give me your phone.
这人很多  你不觉得吗
It's kind of busy here, don't you think?
有目击者是好事
Well, witnesses are good.
目击者能提供压力  知道吗
Witnesses are pressure, all right?
一旦你完全吓住了她
Now, once you've got her good and rattled,
然后你就打电话叫救护车
then you call for an ambulance,
但实际上  你是在给我打电话
but really, you're calling for me.
我在你快速拨号的第一个
I'm number one on your speed dial,
就在你的大麻贩子的旁边
right next to your weed dealer.
你打给我  我会火速赶来
You call me. I hotfoot it over here.
我只是"恰好"开车路过
I just "happen" to be driving by.
我停下看有什么麻烦
I stop to see what the trouble is,
最重要的一点是  你们不认识我
and this is the most important part -- you don't know me.
我们从没见过  知道吗
We've never met. You got it?
-当然  -好的
- Sure. - Okay.
现在  我会是凯特尔曼太太的救星
Now, I'm Mrs. K's white knight.
我们一对一交谈
We go mano a mano.
然后你过来收拾我  狠一点  但不要动手
You light into me, okay? Get nasty. And no touching.
别弄乱发型
Leave the hair alone.
除此之外  自由发挥
But otherwise, you know, open season.
大喊  跺脚  骂我是个混蛋
Yell. Stomp. Call me a douche bag.
我会装作没事
I'm gonna play it cool,
让你一个人在那儿闹
give you back some of the razzmatazz.
一旦她看过了这一出
And once she's seen the fireworks,
你就像折叠椅一样收住
you fold like a lawn chair --
皆大欢喜
happy ending.
我们什么时候拿到钱
When do we get our money?
事后
After.
-事后  -事后吗
- After. - After.
我拿到钱你们就拿到钱
You get paid when I get paid.
我才是推动整个事件发展的人
I'm the rising tide that raises all dinghies.
好了  快速测验  什么车
Now, pop quiz -- what's the car?
水星黑貂休旅车  婴儿屎棕色
Mercury Sable wagon. Baby-poop brown.
-好  你们认识我吗  -不认识
- Okay. Do you know me? - No.
太棒了  上帝与你们同在
Damn straight. Go with god.
我很高兴我恰好路过
Well, I'm just glad I happened to be passing by.
很高兴帮助你  贝茜
Happy to be of help, Betsy.
我能叫你"贝茜"吗
May I call you "Betsy"?
叫我詹姆斯就行了
Please, call me "James."
那孩子没事儿  别担心
Oh, the kid will be fine. Don't worry.
他只是有点儿眼冒金星
He just got his bell rung a little.
我来处理就好了  哦  不
I'll -- I'll handle that. Oh, no.
不行  不行
Oh, no, no.
我没想过因为这事收你的钱
I wouldn't think of, uh, taking your money for this.
挪用公款的案子吗
The embezzlement case?
是的  我很乐意谈谈
Mm, yes, I'd -- I'd be happy to talk it over.
该死
Oh, shit.
警告  警告  两分钟后到
Two-minute warning. Two-minute warning.
收到
Got it.
天哪
Oh, my god!
出什么事了
What happened?
快报警
Call 911.
天呐  卡尔  卡尔
Oh, my god! Cal! Cal!
看着我  你还好吗
Look at me! Are you okay?!
兄弟  给点反应  卡尔  你怎么...
Buddy, say something. Cal, what are you --
人要来了
come on already.
-她在那里做什么呢  -我不知道
- What is she doing in there? - I don't know. Shh.
她是在做三明治吗
Is she making a sandwich?
她的责任心呢
Where's her sense of responsibility?
什么
What?
什么  卧了个大槽
What?! Hey! What the f...
遇上你真巧啊  贝茜
Funny to run into you, Betsy.
我只是在...  四处转转
I was just, uh, strolling the neighborhood.
你...你碰上了事故
You -- you were in accident.
真是...
Oh, it's...
喂
Yeah?
-她撇下我们跑了  -她什么
- She took off on us. - She what?
一切按部就班  伙计
It was textbook, man.
我们成功碰瓷了  但是她却跑了
We were diamonds, but then she just took off.
等等  她...肇事逃逸
Okay, wait. She -- she hit-and-run?
是的  她猛踩油门跑了
That's what I'm saying. She bailed and wailed.
好  你们待在原地等我
O-okay. Just stay where you are. I'll come get you.
不不不  去你的
No, no, no. Screw that, man.
我们跟着她呢
We're following her.
你们...怎么...你们是怎么跟着她的
You're -- how are -- you're following her how?
山人自有妙计
We got our ways, yo.
好好好  新计划  你们认识我的
Okay, okay, okay, new plan -- new plan. You do know me.
我是你们的律师  明白吗
I'm your lawyer. You got that?
我们在学校碰头
I'll meet you at the school.
不  她开过学校了
No, she's way past the school.
她刚刚在胡安·塔布街左转了
She hooked a left on Juan Tabo,
正要去假日公园
and she's coming into Holiday Park.
好  跟着她
O-okay, stay with her.
等她到了目的地  不管是哪里
When she gets where she's going, wherever that is,
什么都别做
just don't do anything.
-等我来  -等什么等
- Wait for me. - Wait for what?
你哪次说对过
You haven't been right even once!
风流你个头吉米
Slippin' Jimmy, my ass!
你们撞大运了  孩子
You fell into the honeypot, kid.
你明白吗  肇事逃逸可是重罪
You get it? Hit-and-run is a felony.
所以呢
So what?
"所以呢"  所以就有更多的钱
"So what?" So more money.
他说我们撞大运了  还说"更多的钱"
He says we fell in the honeypot. He says "More money."
所以我们还要他干什么呢
So what do we need him for?
卡尔  拉斯  你们谁...该死
Cal? Lars? Whoever -- oh, damn it!
拜托  拜托
Come on. Come on!
-来啊  来啊  -狗娘养的
- Do it. Do it. Do it. - Son of a bitch!
拜托
Come on!
你的腿  这回交给我吧
Hey. Hey, your leg. Oh, I'm gonna do this one.
-好  -喂喂喂
- Okay. - Hey! Aah! Aah!
等一等
Hey, yo, hold up.
没错  就是你  你怎么回事
Hey, yeah, you -- what is the matter with you?
你肇事逃逸了
You hit-and-run.
你撞伤了他  你重罪了我弟弟
You ran him over. You felonied my brother.
-出什么事了  -讲英语
- ?Qué pasa? - Habla english.
我们...我们已经报警了
We call -- we call la policía.
警察会很生气的
La policía gonna be pissed.
我看见你撞他了
I see you hit him.
你看那个...那个挡风玻璃  都是你干的
You see that -- that windshield? You did that.
-听不懂  听不懂  -我干的
- No entiendo. No entiendo. - I did that.
你撞了我  你撞了我  你得付钱
You did that to me. You did that. Now you pay.
-先生  我听不懂  -付钱就能解决
- No, se?or. No, se?or. No entiendo. - Make with the dinero.
-钱吗  -钱
- ?Dinero? - Dinero.
对  我们要的是正当钱
Sí, righteous dinero.
-钱  -对...没错
- Dinero? - Y-- sí.
-好  -对  我说的就是这个
- Okay. - Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
-就是这个  -孩子
- Talking about. - Mijo.
我们走
Let's go.
孩子
Mijo!
-是钱吧  -是
- Is that money? - Yeah.
孩子
Mijo...
小心台阶
watch this step.
小心...小心这级台阶
Aah. Watch this -- watch this step.
你们在哪里
Where are you?
假日公园
Holiday Park.
凯特尔曼夫人  贝茜
Mrs. Kettleman, Betsy.
你们在这做什么呢
What are you doing here?
肇事逃逸  那可是重罪
Hit-and-run? That's very serious.
我可以...我可以调解
I can -- I can mediate.
我...我代表他们父母  所以...
It's -- I represent their parents, so...
拜托  拜托
Come on. Come on.
开门  我是法院工作人员
Open up! Officer of the court!
以法律之名  命你开门
Open up in the name of the law!
下午好  这...
Good afternoon. This --